Great, we'll bring you back a T-shirt.
SHELDON:
Thank you.
Hello, neighbor.
(Penny:)Hello, Sheldon.
And how are you this fine evening?
(Leonard:)- Great.
- Good, I'm glad.
PENNY:
Really? Are you drunk?
(Sheldon:)I'm just in a good mood.
(Sheldon:)While my compatriots are in Las Vegas...
(Sheldon:)...I will be enjoying a blissful evening
in my personal Fortress of Solitude.
That's Superman's big ice thingy, right?
You know, I'm in such a good mood,
I'm actually finding your tenuous grasp...
(Sheldon:)...of the English language
folksy and charming today.
(Penny:)Mmm. What smells so good?
(Sheldon:)That is the intoxicating aroma
of Kadhai Paneer.
(Sheldon:)A perfect culinary representation
of the freedom this evening holds.
(Sheldon:)Not only is it Indian cuisine,
which Koothrappali loathes...
(Sheldon:)...it contains a generous helping
of peanuts...
(Sheldon:)...which would reduce Wolowitz
to a wheezing 97-pound blister.